Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Gottfried Baking Co., Inc. vs. Local 802, IBT, 6/24/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Decision - Duty to Bargain, Compensation, Back Pay Awards
- Lundy Electronics & Systems vs. Local 431, IUE, 6/24/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Decision - Overtime, Schedules of Work
- Murray Manufacturing Corp. vs. Local 365, UAW, 7/5/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Decision - Seniority, Transfers
- Flushing Hospital vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 7/23/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Decision - Suspension, Insubordination, Improper Personal Conduct, Remedies
- David Livingston, as President of District 65, RWDSU vs. Textile Converters Assn., Inc. on behalf of Renour Fabrics, Inc., 8/11/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Sealtest Foods, Inc. vs. Local 607, IBT, 8/27/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper Personal Conduct
- Empty (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Henry S. Levy & Sons, Inc. vs. Local 3, BCW, 9/27/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Decision - Intra-Union Disputes, Authority of Representative
- Chalib Restaurant vs. Local 158, Bartenders, 9/30/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Pall Corp. vs. Local 365, UAW, 9/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  Decision - Assignment of Work Outside Classification, Evaluation of Job Factors, Classification of Jobs
- Millard Fillmore Hospital vs. Buffalo & Western NY Hospital and Nursing Home Organizing Committee, 10/4/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Fights and Altercations
- Cosmos Industries, Inc. vs. Local 815, IBT, 10/18/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Absences
- R.H. Macy & Co., Inc. vs. Local 1-S, RWDSU, 10/18/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Consolidated Engravers Inc. vs. Local 8, IWESDWU, 4/12/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 1)
- American ORT Federation vs. Local 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees, 4/13/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 2)
- Greater New York Plumbing and Heating Supply Jobbers Association, Inc. vs. Local 1146, RCIA, 4/18/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 3)
- Plumbing and Heating Wholesalers Employees Association Inc., vs. Local 1146, RCIA, 4/19/55 (Box 3.1, Folder 4)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Vacation, Welfare Fund, Pension Fund, Seniority, Discharge
- Associated Grocers of Harlem Inc. and Lincoln Market vs. Local 338, RWDSU, 4/22/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 5)
  Decision - Overtime
- A & A Wine Works vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 4/28/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 6)
- Educational Alliance vs. Local 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees' Union, 5/5/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 7)
  Decision - Vacation Pay
- American Cellubox Corporation, vs. Local 875, IBT, 5/20/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 8)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Standard of Production, Dishonesty
- Interborough News Co. vs. Local 20650, Vending Machine Service Employees, 5/23/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 9)
  Decision - Discharge.
- Metal Industries, Inc. vs. Local 1227, UE, 5/25/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 10)
- Metropolitan Opera Association vs. Local 1115-C Amusement Clerks and Concessionaires Employees Union, 6/17/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 11)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Duration of Agreement
- Mayrock Silver Co. vs. Local 853, Retail Furniture and Floor Covering Employees Union, 6/25/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 12)
- Sanitary Dash Corporation vs. Local 475, UE, 7/25/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 13)
- Sun Chemical Co., vs. Local 1482, Paintmakers Union, 7/26/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 14)
  Decision - Discharge, Insubordination, Improper Job Attitude
- Par Motor Parts vs. Local 259, UAW, 7/27/55., 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 15)
- 2527 Valentine Avenue vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 7/27/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 16)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Holidays, Vacation
- Air Con Service, Inc. vs. Local 638, Enterprise Association, Metal Trades Branch, 8/4/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 17)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Dress
- J.T. Whalen, Inc. vs. Local 138, IBT, 8/4/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 18)
  Decision - Representation
- National Sleep Products, Inc. vs. Local 140, Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Union, 9/15/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Vacations
- World Metal Spinning Co. vs. Metal Spinners and Silver-Plated Hollow-Ware Workers Union, 9/21/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 20)
- Duracold Corporation vs. Local 150, United Mechanics Union, 9/21/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 21)
- Charlie Seretan Trading Co. and John and Frank's Clothing Store Operated by Johnny, Frank and Charlie, Inc. vs. Harlem Labor Union, 10/19/55 (Box 3.1, Folder 22)
- Bayer Cadillac and Olds Inc., vs. Local 259, UAW, 10/25/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 23)
- James DePoian vs. Local 1, Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union, 11/10/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 24)
  Decision - Discharge, Standards of Production
- Suburban-in-Hewlett, Inc. vs. Local 1115, Restaurant and Luncheonette Employees, 11/10/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Discharge, Contract Interpretation
- Cosmopolitan Studies, Inc. vs. Local 24910, Blueprint, Photostat and Photo Employees Union, 11/18/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 26)
- Daniel Jones, Inc. vs. Local 853, RWDSU, 11/21/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 27)
  Decision - Compensation, Assignment of Jobs
- Myrtle Maintenance Corporation vs. Cornelia Taxi Employees Welfare Association, 11/29/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Decision - Suspension, Carelessness and Negligence
- Applicator Brush Co., Inc. vs. Local 432, Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, (OCAWIU), 10/30/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 29)
  Decision - Discharge, Fights and Altercations
- Benrus Watch Co., Inc. vs. Local 121, International Jewelry Workers Union, 11/30/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 30)
- 570-78 West 193rd Street vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/13/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 31)
- Metro Stores, Inc. vs. District 65, DPOW, 12/13/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 32)
- El Morocco, vs. Local 1, Dining Room Employees, 12/21/55, 1955 (Box 3.1, Folder 33)
- National Sleep Products, Inc. vs. Local 140, Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Workers Union, 1/3/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 34)
- Bilt-Rite Mattress Co., Inc. vs. Local 140, Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Workers Union, 1/13/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 35)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Salary Schedule
- Union Coal and Oil Co. vs. Local 638, Metal Trades Branch, 1/16/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 36)
- Shell-Craft Manufacturing Corporation vs. Local 408, United Optical Workers Union (UOWU), 1/16/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 37)
  Decision - Vacation Pay, Rates of Pay, Duration of Agreement.
- Sonotone Corporation vs. Local 428, UE, 1/20/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 38)
- Frank's Super Markets, Inc. vs. Local 338, Retail, Wholesale and Chain Store Food Employees Union, 1/20/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 39)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Insubordination
- Hill's Supermarkets, Inc. vs. Local 1500, Retail Food Clerks, 2/9/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 40)
- Peerless Sample Card Company, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 2/20/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 41)
- I.D. Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 147, RWDSU, 3/8/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 42)
- Arbuck, Inc. vs. Local 475, UE, 3/14/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 43)
- Restaurant League of N.Y., Inc. vs. Local 15, Bartenders Union, 3/14/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 44)
- Gary Quilting Corporation, Sajan Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. Local 815, IBT, 3/23/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 45)
  Decision - Pension Plan, Rates of Pay
- Lantor Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 4/5/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 46)
  Decision - Discharge, Rates of Pay
- Gem Metal Spinning and Stamping Co., Inc. vs. Local 49, International Jewelry Workers Union, (IJWU), 4/24/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 47)
- Gary Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 5/2/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 48)
- C.B. Cotton and Co., Inc. vs. Local 222, IJWU, 5/2/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 49)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Tardiness
- Livingston Sales, Inc. vs. Local 138, IBT, 5/11/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 50)
- Continental Baking vs. Local 50, BCW, 5/29/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 51)
  Decision - Seniority, Promotion
- Beigel Bakers Association vs. Local 338, Beigel Baker Union, 5/31/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 52)
  Decision - Insurance (Workmen's Compensation)
- Spic and Span Auto laundry vs. Local 5, UAW, 6/1/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 53)
- Custom Craft Die Cutting Corporation vs. Local 107 Labor-management Trust Fund, 6/1/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 54)
- Electrical Insulation Corporation vs. Local 431, UE, 6/11/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 55)
- Flight Foods Inc. vs. Local 501, Transport Workers Union (TWU), 6/26/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 56)
  Decision - Discipline, Improper Job Attitude
- DuMidi Bar, Inc. vs. Local 1, Dining Room Employees, 7/9/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 57)
  Decision - Leaves of Absence
- Long Island Mattress Co. vs. Local 140, Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Workers Union, 7/10/56, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 58)
- Salvatore J. Giresi, d/b/a Bonanza Drywall Co. vs. Local 964, Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, 10/28/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Decision - Identification of Employer, Contractual Duties
- A. Goodman & Sons, Inc. vs. Local 269, CIUA, 11/7/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Paterson Caterers vs. Local 158, Bartenders, Culinary Workers, 11/7/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs
- Metromedia, Inc., Licensee of Radio Stations WNEW and WNEW-FM vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 12/1/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- City of New York, The Doctors Association of the Department of Health of the City of New York, 12/15/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Finding of Fact and Recommendations - Working Conditions [Rates of Pay, Compensation, Welfare Fund, Sick Leave, Sick Pay]
- Airequipt Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. District 15, IAM, 12/19/66 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Gambling
- Modern Maintenance, Inc. vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 12/30/66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Decision - Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- New York Post Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1/3/67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Kings Highway Medical Group vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 1/5/67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs, Classification of Jobs, Seniority, Schedules of Work
- Micro Lectric, Inc. vs. Local 1922, IBEW, 1/10/67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Decision - Union Security, Arbitration Procedure
- Vulcap Corp. vs. Local 721, Retailmen's Wear, Sporting Goods and Accessories Union, 1/25/67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Hills Brothers Coffee Co. vs. Local 660, IBT, 2/2/67. #67-243, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Decision - Seniority
- City of New York vs. Social Service Employees Union, 3/15/67. #67-244 (Folders A-H), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Findings of Fact and Recommendations, Hearing Transcripts, Union Exhibits, Fact-Finder's Notes on Case - Rates of Pay
- Daitch Crystal Dairies, Inc. vs. Local 277, IBT, 7/17/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 1)
- Ackerman Gould Company, vs. Local 477, IUE, 7/25/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 2)
- Beegee Transportation Corporation vs. Local 814, IBT, 7/25/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 3)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Holiday Pay, Vacation
- Nu-Batts Corporation vs. Local 140, UFW, 7/25/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 4)
  Decision - Pension Fund
- Legion Cabinet Corporation vs. Local 3127, UBCJA, 8/9/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 5)
  Decision - Holiday Pay, Lay-off
- East New York Lumber Company, vs. Local 1205, IBT, 8/20/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 6)
- Universal Auto Radiator vs. District 15, IAM, 9/14/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 7)
- Dee Dee Products Company, Local 199, UAW, 9/14/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 8)
- Duracold, Inc. vs. Local 150, United Mechanics Union, 9/20/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 9)
- 1166 Manor Avenue vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 9/21/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 10)
  Decision - Discharge, Severance Pay
- North American Iron and Steel Co., vs. Local 66, Architectural and Engineering Guild, 9/24/56., 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 11)
  Decision - Bargaining Units, Classification of Jobs
- West Side T.V. Company vs. Local 854, UFW, 10/3/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 12)
  Decision - Welfare Fund, Severance Pay, Vacation Pay
- 1034-38 Tiffany Street vs. Local 670, Stationary Engineers, 10/9/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 13)
  Decision - Discharge, Incompetency and Inefficiency
- Premier Metal Products vs. District 50, UMW, 10/10/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 14)
- Ditmas 21st Corporation vs. Local 377, RWDSU, 10/11/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 15)
  Decision - Discharge, Alcoholism, Improper Work Practices
- Acme Quilting Company, Inc. vs. Local Textile Workers of America, (TUWA), 10/16/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 16)
  Decision - Super-seniority, Standards of Production
- Drago Stores, Inc. vs. Local 563, Shoe Services Union, 11/1/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 17)
- Mechanical Steel Tubing vs. Local 365, UAW, 11/8/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 18)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Cost of Living Increases
- Rose Embroidery Corporation, Herbert L. Rose, vs. Local 66, International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 11/15/56., 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Welfare Funds.
- Paul Furman d/b/a Kingston Brush Manufacturing Company vs. Local 16303, Brushmakers Union, 11/15/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 20)
  Decision - Contract Negotiations, Rates of Pay, Vacation
- Fischer-Stevens, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 11/19/56 (Box 4.1, Folder 21)
  Decision - Sick Pay
- Lifton, Gold and Asher vs. District 65, RWDSU, 11/19/56 (Box 4.1, Folder 22)
- Crown Drug Stores, Inc. vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 11/26/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 23)
  Decision - Discharge, Negligence and Carelessness
- Trocchio Carting Co. vs. Local 95, House Wreckers' Union, 11/30/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 24)
  Decision - Pension and Welfare Funds, Contracting out
- Mabar Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/5/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Discharge, Inability to Work
- Re-Ly-On Metal Products vs. Local 150, United Mechanics, 12/6/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 26)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Welfare and Pension Funds
- Mamaroneck T.V. Co., Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 12/18/56, 1956 (Box 4.1, Folder 27)
- National Gypsum Company vs. District 50, UMW, 1/8/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Job Description - Rates of Pay
- Fisher-Stevens, Inc., vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/11/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 29)
- Empire Phonograph vs. Coin Machine Employees Union, 1/22/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 30)
  Decision - Financial Irresponsibility
- Hill's Supermarkets, Inc. vs. Local 342, Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees, 2/20/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 31)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Call-in
- Specialty Assembling and Packing Co., vs. Local 431, IUE, 3/14/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 32)
  Decision - Grievance Procedure
- Whale Steel Equipment vs. Local 150 United Mechanics Union, 3/19/57 (Box 4.1, Folder 33)
- 53 Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 3/19/57 (Box 4.1, Folder 34)
- Louis Schweller vs. Local 29, Bronx Bartenders Union, 3/22/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 35)
- Sperry Gyroscope Co., Division of Sperry Rand Corporation vs. Local 3, IBEW, Local's 450 and 470, IUE, 4/2/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 36)
  Decision - Assignment of jobs
- Hamburg Heaven, Inc. vs. Local 302, Cafeteria Employees Union, 4/9/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 37)
  Decision - Discharge, Negligence and Carelessness, Absences
- Champion Envelope Company vs. Local 210, IBT, 4/11/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 38)
  Decision - Discharge, Vacation, Severance Pay
- B.R. Trucking Company vs. Local 202, IBT, 4/25/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 39)
- Pas Wrecking and Lumber Company, Inc. vs. Local 95, House Wreckers Union, 5/8/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 40)
  Decision - Union Security
- Linden Curtain Company vs. Harlem Labor Union, 6/5/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 41)
- 1105 Boynton Avenue vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/5/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 42)
  Decision - Discharge, dishonesty
- 570 W. 193rd Street Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/7/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Welfare Fund
- Anthony Guisto Company, Inc. vs. Local 522, IBT, 6/20/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 44)
- George Bell, d/b/a George Bell Spring and Metal Works vs. Local 10, International Brotherhood of Production Maintenance and Operating Employees, 6/20/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 45)
- Forest Park Cooperative, Inc. vs. Local 670, Stationary Engineers, 6/21/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 46)
- Kelton Cosmetics Company vs. Local 815, IBT, 7/2/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 47)
- Highland Amusement Company vs. Local 26, IJWU, 7/2/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 48)
- Ford Instrument Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corp. vs. Local 425, IUE, 7/10/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 49)
  Decision - Discharge, Suspension
- Ford Instrument Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corp. vs. Local 425, IUE, 7/17/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 50)
  Decision - Alcoholism.
- Carnell Manufacturing Co., Local 35, Leather and Novelty Workers of Greater NY, 8/5/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 51)
- Sunset Appliance Stores vs. Local 854, IBT, 8/7/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 52)
- Norton Retail Stores, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 8/8/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 53)
  Decision - Layoff, Severance Pay, Financial Irresponsibility
- Franklin Market vs. Local 342, Retail Food Store Employees Union, 8/20/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 54)
  Decision - Welfare and Pension Funds
- Nelson Brothers, Metal Ornaments vs. Local 222, IJWU, 8/23/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 55)
- Duralite Company, Inc. vs. Local 222, IGWU, 8/23/57, 1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 56)
  Decision - Discharge, Classification of Jobs, Rates of Pay
- Compass Van and Storage Corp. vs. Local 814, IBT, 3/16/67. #67-245, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Decision - Reinstatement, Medical Release
- Pall Corp. vs. Local 365, UAW, 7/3/67. #67-246, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Decision - Transfers, Schedules of Work
- J.S. Carelick Parkside Memorial Chapel, Inc. vs. Local 407, BSEIU, 5/2/67. #67-247, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Decision - Union Security, Evaluation of Job Factors, Supervisors and Foremen
- Morsen Farmingdale Inc. vs. District 15, 2/14/67. #67-248, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Decision - Discharge Insubordination
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 5/67. #67-253, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cluett, Peabody & Co., Inc. vs. ACWA, 7/3/67. #67-254, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Decision - Rates of Pay (Change Time)
- Rosett Chemicals Inc. vs. Local 1310, Paintmakers, 4/12/67. #67-257, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Decision - Holidays and Holiday Pay
- New York Post Corp. vs. Local 3, Newspaper Guild of New York, 10/26/67. #67-259, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Decision - Schedules of Work
- Eaton Yale & Towne, Inc. Trojan Division vs. Local 78, IAMSOIW, 5/11/67. #67-260, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Decision - Management Rights, Schedules of Work, Past Practice
- General Airline and Film Corp. vs. Local 306, ICWU, 5/31/67. #67-261, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Decision - Overtime, Assignment of Jobs
- Hess Oil & Chemical Corp. vs. Local 22026, Federal Labor Union, 6/16/67. #67-267, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Decision - Assignment to Work Outside Classification, Duty to Bargain
- Publix Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 6/22/67. #67-268, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Decision - Timeliness, Application for Employment (Transfer)
- Lily Tulip Cup Co. vs. District 47, IAM, 6/12/67. #67-271, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Laundry Worker jt. Board of ACWA vs. Local 400, N.Y. Joint Board, 5/19/67. #67-272 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Decision - Discharge, Retirement, Remedies
- Nice-Pak Products, Inc. vs. Local 1, IJWU, 5/23/67, #67-275, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc. vs. ACWA, 5/67. #67-273, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Suburban Foods, Inc. vs. Local 1S, RWDSU, 5/67. #67-274, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Decision - Discharge, Discipline, Suspension, Falsification
- Sherry Pharmaceutical Corp. vs. Local 815, IBT, 6/5/67. #67-277, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Business Letter Service vs. District 65, RWDSU, 8/30/67. #67-278, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Decision - Supervisors and Foremen, Evaluation of Job Factors
- N.Y. Athletic Club vs. Local 6, Hotel and Club Employees' Union, 6/5/67. #67-279, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Quaker Industries, Inc. vs. IJWU, 6/67. #67-280, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Barash Co., Inc. vs. Local 210, IBT, 6/26/67. #67-281, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Decision - Vacation Pay, Discharge, Absences
- Vulcan Materials Co. vs. Local 575, IBT, 9/23/67. #67-282, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Classification of Jobs, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Eazor Express Co. vs. Local 560, IBT, 7/3/67. #67-283, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Nesco Steel Barrel Co. vs. Local 1034, IBT, 6/67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Decision - Discharge, Incompetence & Inefficiency, Improper Job Attitude, overtime
- Pan American World Airlines vs. Local 504, TWU, 7/5/67. #67-288, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Decision - Discharge, Leaves of Absence
- Hempstead Bus Corp. vs. Amalgamated Assn. of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Div. 1511, 8/11/67 & 10/2/67. #67-290, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Vacations, Vacation Pay
- Direct Mail Master Contract Assn. Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 9/11/67. #67-291, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Decision - Severance Pay, Contract Interpretation
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. Local 143, IAM, 12/29/67. #67-292, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Union Labor Life Insurance Co. vs. Local 153, Office Employees International Union, 9/67. #67-293, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Gimbel Brothers, Inc., Valley Stream vs. District 65, RWDSU, 9/1/67. #67-294, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Decision - Discharge, Violence
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corp. vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT), 10/16/67. #67-296, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Decision - Arbitration Procedure
- Sealtest Foods, Inc. vs. Local 607, IBT, 8/25/67. #67-298, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Decision - Seniority, Assignment of Jobs
- Merganthaler Linotype vs. Local 365, UAW, 9/12/67. #67-299, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Decision - Improper Personal Conduct
- Schwerman Trucking Co. vs. Local 294, IBT, 11/27/67. #67-300, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Decision - Dishonesty, Absenteeism
- Whittaker, Clark & Daniels, Inc. vs. Local 641, IBT, 10/3/67. #67-301, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Decision - Absences, Tardiness
- Rhodia, Inc. vs. Local 8-622, OCAWIU, 9/27/67. #67-302, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Decision - Altercation
- Rowe Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 950, UAW, 11/8/67. #67-304, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Decision - Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems
- J.S. Garlick Parkside Memorial Chapel, Inc. vs. Local 407, BSEIU, 9/25/67. #67-307, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Decision - Conflict Over Opinion of the Law
- Hi-Torc Motor Corp. vs. Local 431, IUE, 9/25/67. #67-308, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Decision - Insubordination
- Hi-Torc Motor Corp. vs. Local 431, IUE, 9/25/67. #67-309, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Decision - Reporting Pay
- Ettco Tool and Machine Co., Inc. vs. District 15, IAM, 9/13/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 1)
- Associated Barber Shops, Inc. vs. Local 760, Journeymen, Barbers, Hairdressers and Cosmetologists International Union, 9/18/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
- Messing Bakeries, Inc. vs. Local 802, IBT, 10/3/57., 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 3)
- Lincoln School of Radio and Television, Inc. vs. Local 2, New York Teachers Guild, 10/16/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 4)
- J. Cantor Shoes, vs. Local 305, RWDSU, 10/17/57., 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 5)
- Clary Corporation vs. Local 459, IUE, 10/22/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 6)
- Bias Fabric Manufacturers Association, Inc. vs. TWUA, 10/28/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 7)
- Art Craft Die Cutters and Embossers, Inc. vs. Local 447, IBPSPMW, 10/30/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 8)
  Decision - Vacation Pay, Rates of Pay, Welfare Fund
- Superior Meter Co., Inc. vs. Local 365, UAW, 10/30/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 9)
  Decision - Holiday and Vacation Pay
- Lincoln School of Radio and Television Inc. vs. Local 2, Teachers Guild, 11/13/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 10)
  Decision - Back Pay Award